旋转电动机可以通过该电气原理图建模。重要组成部分
A rotary electric motor can be modelled by this electrical schematic. Important components
该型号的电阻是电阻，这是电枢线圈的电阻。
of the model are a resistor and this is the resistance of the armature coil.
那是转子中的电磁铁。另一个组件是电压源。电机
That's the electromagnet in the rotor. The other component is a voltage source. A motor
可以反向用作发电机，但即使它作为电动机发电机也是如此
can be used in reverse as a generator but even when it's acting as a motor the generator
产生的电压与施加的电压相反，这被称为背面
is producing a voltage that opposes the applied voltage and this is referred to as the back
EMF。并且该电压与电动机的转速成比例。
EMF. And this voltage is proportional to the rotational speed of the motor.
流入电动机的电流由施加的电压之差给出
The current that flows into the motor is given by the difference between the applied voltage
费用和反电动势电压VB除以电枢电阻RA。
fee and the back EMF voltage VB divided by the armature resistance RA.
电机产生的转矩与流过电机的电流成正比
The torque generated by the motor is proportional to the current that flows through the motor
比例常数是KM。这两个KM虽然具有完全相同的价值
and the proportionality constant is KM. These two KMs have exactly the same value though
它们通常用不同的单位编写。这里的这个单位为伏特秒
they're written typically with different units. This one here has units of volts seconds per
弧度。这里有一个牛顿米每安培的单位，但需要一点努力
radian. This one here has units of Newton meters per Amp but with a little bit of effort
你可以证明这两个单位实际上是等价的。
you can show that these two units are in fact equivalent.
有两种方法可以控制电动机。我们可以控制电压或者我们可以
There are two ways to control an electric motor. We can control the voltage or we can
控制当前。
control the current.
让我们首先看看电压控制情况。所以我们要调整电压
Let's first of all look at the voltage control case. So we're going to adjust the voltage
我们应用于电机，我们可以使用功率放大器或类似的东西
that we apply to the motor and we can do that using a power amplifier or something like
带调制器的脉冲。我们很快就会看到这一点。我写下了所有相关内容
a pulse with modulator. And we'll look at that shortly. I've written down all the relevant
等式，如果我重新排列这个等式，我们可以得到旋转的表达式
equation and if I rearrange this equation we can get an expression for the rotational
速度欧姆加在施加电压方面的电流等。
speed omega in terms of the applied voltage the current and so on.
想象一下，电机在静止时启动，我施加电压，电流和电机
Imagine that the motor starts at rest and I apply a voltage, current flows and the motor
将开始加快速度。正如它所做的那样，反电动势将最终增加
will start to increase in speed. As it does so the back EMF will increase and eventually
反电动势将等于施加的电压，然后没有电流流入
the back EMF will be equal to the applied voltage and then no current will flow into
电机。然后电机将停止加速，当发生这种情况时，我们会有一个简单的表达式
the motor. The motor will then stop accelerating and when this occurs we have a simple expression
对于Omega，它是施加的电压除以电机常数。
for Omega it's the applied voltage divided by the motor constant.
现在在实践中，电机已经摩擦，并且在实践中使得电机的速度更快
Now in practice the motor has got friction and in practice that makes the speed of the
电机小于此处显示的值。重要的是拿走了速度
motor less than the value shown here. The important take away is that the speed of the
电动机与施加的电压成比例。最常见的驱动电动机的方法
motor is proportional to the applied voltage. The most common way to drive an electric motor
今天是所谓的H桥电路。它包括四个开关，它们通常是
today is with what's called an H bridge circuit. It comprises four switches and they’re typically
某种场效应晶体管。它们非常小，而且非常有效
some kind of field effect transistor. They're very small and they're very efficient when
他们关闭了他们有一个非常小的阻力。
they're closed they have a very very small resistance.
如图所示，没有电流可以流过电机但是如果我关闭其中两个开关
As shown here no current can flow through the motor but if I close two of the switches
然后我们看到电流将在一个特定的方向流过电机
then we see the current will flow through the motor in one particular direction and
电机将向前旋转。如果我打开那两个开关并关闭
the motor will rotate in the forward direction. If I open those two switches and close the
另外两个，电流在另一个方向上流过电动机，电动机向后旋转。
other two, current flows in the other direction through the motor and the motor rotates backwards.
这些电子馈电开关的一个优点是我们可以打开和关闭它们
One of the advantages of these electronic fed switches is that we can them on and off
很快。施加到电机的电压可以是一段时间内的最大值
very quickly. The voltage that's applied to the motor can be the maximum value for a time
我们称之为准时的时期，我们称之为的时期为零
period which we refer to as the on time and there can zero for what we refer to as the
关闭时间。并且驱动H桥电路的电子设备能够控制
off time. And the electronics which is driving the H bridge circuit is able to control the
占空比。这是导通时间与周期的比率，这可能与电压不同
duty cycle. That's the ratio of the on time to the period and this can vary from the voltage
始终关闭始终打开的电压。
being always off to the voltage being always on.
电机响应平均电压。所以这是一个占空比的例子
The motor responds to the average voltage. So here's an example where the duty cycle
相对较低的是电压关闭的时间比开启的时间长。和电机
is relatively low that is the voltage is off for more time than it is on. And the motor
当我增加占空比时，我看到红线所示的有效平均电压
sees an effective average voltage shown by the red line as I increase the duty cycle
平均电压上升，我可以进一步增加占空比。
the average voltage rises and I can increase the duty cycle even further.
因此，通过调整微控制器可以很容易地完成的占空比，
So by adjusting the duty cycle which is something that a micro controller can do quite easily,
我们可以以几乎连续的方式控制平均电压。这种转换发生了
we can control the average voltage in an almost continuous fashion. This switching happens
非常非常快，通常频率至少为1kHz。
very very quickly, typically a frequency of at least 1 kHz.
控制电动机的另一种方法是调节流过的电流
An alternative way of controlling the electric motor is to regulate the current that flows
进入电机。有许多方法可以创建控制电流源。
into the motor. There are many ways to create a control current source.
常见的方法是采用控制电压源并施加电流反馈回路。
A common way is to take a control voltage source and apply a current feedback loop.
电动机产生的转矩与流过电动机的电流成比例。
The torque generated by the motor is proportional to the current flowing through the motor.
扭矩也等于电动机的转动惯量乘以其转动
The torque is also equal to the rotational inertia of the motor multiplied by its rotational
加速。这是等式F=MA的旋转等效。现在我们可以写一个
acceleration. This is the rotational equivalent of the equation F = MA. Now we can write an
根据流入电动机的电流表示电动机的旋转加速度。
expression for the rotational acceleration of the motor in terms of the current flowing into the motor.